ILR School Strategic Planning Committee Files /4281
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Strategic Planning Committee Files
1966-1996
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4281
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents), case files.
8072413
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 02, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Strategic planning; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Strategic Planning Committee
8072413
- Reports, Minutes, Correspondence. (Box 1)
  - Ileen Devault, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Report on Strategic Planning, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1/12 re 1/20, 2/44 2/20, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ileen Devault 292 Ives, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Memorandums, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ILR Memorandums, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ILR Faculty Commissions, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Mtgs. Of SP Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meetings of SP Committee, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ILR Strategic Planning, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Instruction Subcommittee #1, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - SP - Instruction Subcommittee, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - BKGD for SP Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Misc., 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Inst. Sub-Committee "DATA", 1966-1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 93/94 Travel Docs for SP Mtgs., 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Outside Review, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Outside Review, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)